https://www.kangaroobie.com/privacy/

HomeProgramsFive Day ProgramThree Day ProgramEducation ProgramsActivitiesBookingsKangaroobieAccommodationFoodWhat to BringHistoryInformationStudentsParentsTeachersLocationEnvironmentFind usLocal AttractionsContactContact usBookings
Privacy
Kangaroobie recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to this website.
By using this website, you agree to the privacy policy set out below. This policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through your use of this website.
Personal Information
Personal information about visitors to this website is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in Australia.
Use of Information
Personal information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted. Copies of correspondence sent from the website, that may contain personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back-up purposes only.
Cookies
This website uses cookies for security purposes in password protected areas of the website.
Disclosure
Apart from where you have consented, or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations. In the unlikely event of an investigation, a law enforcement agency or other government agency may exercise its legal authority to inspect our logs and databases.
Security
This site does not provide facilities for the secure transmission of information across the Internet. Users should be aware that there are inherent risks transmitting information across the Internet.
However, we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.
Access to Information
We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, please contact us to have the information corrected.
In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us.
Further Privacy Information
For more information about privacy issues in Australia and protecting your privacy, visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner’s website (www.privacy.gov.au).
Your hosts:
